SADIA WAHEED

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Phone: (+966) 55 8806805 Email: sadia.waheed312@hotmail.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/sadia-waheed

Address: Ar Rawdah, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

Website: https://sadiawaheed.github.io/portfolio/

SUMMARY

A junior programmer who loves to learn. Has been working with C# since 2012, MS SQL Server since 2014 and .NET since 2015 in various school, job and personal projects. Well-versed in Microsoft Stack with some experience in other technologies like Python, Node JS, Angular, and React JS.

EXPERIENCE

INTERNS.PK - REMOTE 02/2023 - 03/2023

Intern for Interns Program

Web app design and development using php and Wordpress

INTERNS.PK - REMOTE 09/2020 - 10/2020

Intern for Spark Program

• Web app development using React JS

SYSTEMS LIMITED - KARACHI, PAKISTAN 01/2018 - 06/2018

Software Engineer

- Developed new modules for product (SysHCM).
- · Wrote technical reports for all development.
- · Performed unit testing on all developed modules.
- · Trained and guided Juniors on product.

SYSTEMS LIMITED - KARACHI, PAKISTAN

03/2017 - 01/2018

Associate Software Engineer

- Developed new modules for product (SysHCM).
- Wrote technical reports for all development.
- · Performed unit testing on all developed modules.

PAKISTAN INTERNATIONAL AIRLINES - KARACHI, PAKISTAN

01/2016 - 01/2018

Intern

· Developed .NET forms application for domestic cargo management.

EDUCATION

INSTITUTE OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (IBA) - KARACHI, PAKISTAN

GPA 3.2 2017 - 2019

BAHRIA UNIVERSITY - KARACHI, PAKISTAN

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Master of Computer Science

GPA 3.6 2012 - 2016

SKILLS

C#, .NET, Razor, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Web API, React, Angular, Node.js, PostgreSQL, Microsoft SQL, Software Designs, Bootstrap, Python, Model View Controller, Entity Framework, OOP, UML, and Code Reviews

TOOLS

Microsoft Visual Studio Code, Microsoft Visual Studio, Microsoft SQL Server, Postman, #Slack, Trello, Jira, GitHub, and Pg Admin.

PROJECTS

06/2023

Uses Clarify API to detect faces in given pictures. • Tools: React, CSS, JavaScript, VS Code, Git Hub, NodeJS and PostgreSQL

ROBO FRIENDS 05/2023

· A complete React application using Robo friends API.

Tools: React, CSS, JavaScript, JSX, VS Code and Git Hub

09/2022

Online Ordering, Order Management, Online Payments, Product Management, User roles and much more.

• Tools: C#, MS SQL Server, MS Visual Studio, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Stripe payment

COURSES & CERTIFICATES

UDEMY: THE COMPLETE WEB DEVELOPER IN 2023: ZERO TO MASTERY 2023 **UDEMY:** COMPLETE GUIDE TO ASP. NET CORE MVC (.NET 6) 2022 **UDEMY: THE COMPLETE ASP. NET MVC 5 COURSE** 2021

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH (IELTS: 8)

URDU